If you want it, I will protect you.
Don't worry, let's go ahead and go ahead!
To the moon, the moon will
always come to the moon!
The clouds will come and
see the light of the stars.
Let's look at the stars of the stars?
I'll be in the future, so
I'll be in the same way.
Sideline supporter from the first
round, the Savage Chef Sanji.
I think you mean Stylish Chef.
And beside him, with a bounty of 60 million
berries, pirate hunter Robo Noah Zoro.
Hardly worth our time to squash a
couple of pipsqueaks like these.
Right, Big Pan?
I can't hear you.
Man, what do these guys eat?
Well, start this out with a coin toss.
Tails.
Field or ball?
Ball, please. You heard him.
Our groggy monsters have chosen them all.
The Straw Hats Ballman will now enter the
other team's mid-circle, left or right.
Doesn't matter.
In case you were wondering,
the Ballmen are the players with the
silly little hats on their heads.
Knock your opponent's Ballman into
the ring on their side of the field,
and the game is yours.
Just get on with it.
Hey ball man get in
position already now listen
i never agreed to be the
ball in the first place.
You better shut your mouth unless
you want to boot to the teeth.
How am i supposed to look cool with this
thing on my head you're
gonna cry over a hat.
Hey that looks good on you you think
i'm gonna fall for that stupid.
I'm counting on you i'm sorry we lost the
last round you guys it's up to you now.
Please get Chopper back! You got him!
Wow, would you look at that?
It's a real woe-tan.
They aren't as large as pure-blooded
giants, but he's still pretty big.
Don't bother cheering for your friends.
It's no use.
Those guys are more than just a muscle.
They're groggy ring experts.
Oh, hey, split head.
Did you want something?
He said it again.
Oh, poor boss.
Why would you be so cruel
to this sweet, gentle man?
What's with that face?
If you're afraid I'm going to
interfere again, then don't worry.
I won't even need to in
this round, you babies.
Don't tell me you can
butt in on this gang, too.
Yep, it all depends on how
the captain feels. Naturally,
some pilots like to fight fair and square
so they can test the
strength of their crew.
Others will cheat any way they can
to make sure they never lose a match.
But I just do whatever I want.
Hey, hey.
I don't see why you're complaining
about a little foul play here and there.
If you're a real pirate, you should
be used to these sorts of things.
Right?
The sea is treacherous.
Oh, yeah. You would know.
By the way, your team looks to
be playing a game of their own.
They do know the match
is about to start, right?
Three.
Laugh while you still can.
They're just laid back because
they know they can win.
I saw that, cheater.
You went too early on that last one.
Shut up.
You're just mad because you
lost, like you always do. What?
I always lose, huh?
We'll just see about that.
Let's do best three out of five.
And just lose again?
So is the chef your ball man or what?
Hurry up!
Is that what those
idiots are arguing about?
Sanji, that hat looks great on you.
All right, let's rock.
Ball man's here to kick some ass.
I've got to admit, it does suit you.
You look like a real prince
from the kingdom of lame asses.
you're wasting time start the match you
suck no you suck hey hold it no weapons on
the field pal you gotta lose the swords
huh those the rules yeah because this is a
ball game can't have you slicing each
other up now can we
fine my fists are all i
need you sure you're gonna be okay out there
A swordsman without his swords is just,
well, what?
A normal guy, only lamer.
That wasn't even a good bird!
Get over it!
It certainly took long enough,
but it looks like the
Straw Hat's ball man is
finally making his way
to the opponent's circle.
Hey, Cook, hope you
get trampled out there.
Love yours. No!
Get up! No!
The crowd is hungry for action today.
Big Pan, are you ready to
make some grown men cry?
He can't hear you.
Come on, man.
Pay attention for once.
It's not that funny. Stop laughing.
What can I say?
The groggy monsters are
always up for a good laugh.
Now, why don't we go
over a few quick rules.
There's no time limit, and
the first team to score wins.
So all we gotta do to win this is knock
Jumbo's head into the ring on their side.
Simple enough.
Hard part's gonna be stopping them from
planting the cook's head in our ring.
Can team Straw Hat win
back the reindeer they
lost in round one or will
they lose another member?
As you can see foxy's returning champs are
laughing in the face of their competition!
But will they be the ones to laugh
last the whistle is about to sound?
Let the game begin we
start with ball man sanji
deep in enemy territory
will he retreat or attack?
Let's do this tackle
machine pickles takes off
with a heavy charge
okay just gotta head for
Their ball man and finish
him off sling tackle
get out of my way let's
see what you got big man?
I hope that fat head of
yours fits in the goal.
It's going to be a ball
man fight. Oh, yeah.
Hey, what's going on here?
Skin's all slimy.
The chef is slipping and sliding
on Big Pan's massive arm.
But that's no surprise.
After all, Big Pan's a
loach fish, loach hand.
They have slippery skin.
What the heck are you doing?
Stop screwing around. Good and good.
Get down here.
You better watch what
you wish for, sword man.
Long pass.
This is it. Big pan.
Super long pass.
Sludgy.
Team Captain Hamburg races
onto the scene for the catch.
But Zoro is in hot pursuit as well.
If that stupid head of yours
makes it anywhere near the goal,
I'm going to chop it off.
You talk big, but just
wait till I get down there.
Oh, now my sweeping tackle.
Pickles crosses over
the rival team's line.
Meanwhile, Hamburg flies
high for a fancy minute.
Perfect.
And then...
I got it. I got it.
Pickles dashes into position.
Get back here, damn it.
Dorry goes for an interception.
Hehehehe!
Spreading tackle!
Uh-oh!
With his partner down, Ball Bane
Sanji is spiraling into the sky!
Sanji!
Bringing up the rear?
Big pan storms across the field!
and catches the foley ham bird! Ponderous.
Once again, ham bird nabs Sanji
with a perfect catch! Incredible!
The ring is inside!
Is this it?
You can't go down that easy! Yeah!
It's the hamburger dump!
Come about!
Hurry, do something!
Zoro! Find him!
The Straw Hats are running out of time!
I know, I'm honest.
You don't need to remind me.
It ain't over!
I won't let you...
All right, you've had your fun.
Time to put me down, fathead.
I can't let Zoro bail me out of this.
I'd never hear the end of Earth.
And stay down.
Oh, man, Sachi is back on the ground and
looks like he's ready for some more action.
I can take care of myself just fine.
Got it?
If you could stay on the ground, ball.
It seems our groggy monsters have finally
found some worthy adversaries in the ring.
This one will be a match to remember!
Chirp, chirp!
The Straw Hats prevail,
but can they do it again?
We've seen pigs fly once
today, so anything can happen!
The challengers seem to be
discussing their next move.
Let's get ready for round two!
You're cramping my style.
Go back to the sidelines, Mosshead.
Is it your style to get
pounded like a punching bag?
Whoa, dude, they're tough.
That guy picked up
pickles and tossed them!
I've never seen Hamper
go flying like that!
Stay out of the way and I'll win this.
I can't stay out of the way.
I'm the ball man, the
only one that matters.
No!
Hepberg, what are you doing out there?
If you lose, I'll never, ever
forgive you! What's this?
The Straw Hat team seems to be having
some sort of disagreement with each other.
Both ball men are still in play,
so let's hope they can
channel some of that
aggression in a more productive direction.
Those two sure are funny, aren't they?
You idiots!
Now's your chance!
What are you doing?
They're ball-mans all alone!
Gang up on him and knock
him in the ring while
those other guys are
still out of the game!
Whoa!
Big Pan stops him for a surprise
attack on the school hats!
Whoa!
Too bad guys!
Don't run for the ball!
How are you supposed to score?
Hey, I'm doing my best here!
But that guy's got knives on his shoes?
If we don't run away, he's
gonna make mulch out of us!
Hey, ref!
I thought you said we could use weapons!
What?!
He's not even trying,
is he?! Hey, hey, hey!
You can't expect him to catch
every little thing, can you?
Stop!
Screw it around!
Sanji, what were you thinking?
You saw the whole thing.
I saw you sweating over
there, you little cheater.
No, no way.
I didn't see nothing.
Not a thing. You liar.
Hey, that's the riff, Sanji.
You're going to get in trouble.
Yellow card to Sanji of Team Straw Hat.
You want another boot to the face?
Whoa, hold on.
You're only going to make it worse.
And there it is.
A yellow card for Sanji.
Just one more of those,
and the chef will be ejected from
the game once and for all, folks!
Shut up!
I'll eject you!
And the threats keep coming in
from the foul-mouth ball man!
Who knows who he'll lash out at next?
Why don't you come down here
and say that to my face?
What is he, a gangster?
Worry about the boots, the ref can wait.
Wait, an axe?
You can't miss that.
I didn't see.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure!
Look, he's got a giant axe you
can see for yourself, stupid!
Give it up!
You're going to get a red
card if you don't shut it!
Why are you siding with
them all of a sudden?
We're going to get Julienned out there!
I know, but they're trying to
make you do something stupid.
If you won't do it for me,
at least do it for Chopper!
OK, stand back and let me handle him!
No, we don't need the captain
butting in and complicating things!
Dungey, please!
Win the match for me!
I won't let you down!
That was easy.
All right, now back to the game!
If you're gonna do that
again, why even bother?
Running around like this
is getting us nowhere.
Yeah, but now that we know their game
plan, we can come up with a counterattack.
Get ready, big man.
It's payback time!
Go back to the sidelines.
This bastard is mine!
There's plenty of it for the bulk of you!
And they're off!
All three are about to collide!
If I attack him where his skin's exposed,
I'll just end up slipping
around like last time.
That leaves his hands, his feet,
his mask, and his underwear.
Ow!
Here comes Big Pan's signature move!
Things are about to get slippery.
I'll bring it on.
Who's afraid of a little skating, right?
No, there's no escape.
I'm going to lose my life. Come on.
Do it together, guys.
Really?
It looks like Pickles and Hattberg have
finally recovered from
their earlier accident.
Yeah, they're back in it.
Slaughter them, guys.
And what's this?
It seems that they've
updated their wardrobe.
Their leader, Hattberg, is sporting
some iron knuckles and elbow guards.
Where did those come from?
Meanwhile, Pickles has dawned
Spike's shoulder protectors.
Those clearly violate the no-weapons rule.
But by complete coincidence, the referee
seems to be doing some stretches right now.
Oh, well, you can't expect him
to catch up or anything, right?
What?
Time for revenge, my
friend, you ready? The
scrappy
monster
spawns a counterattack,
but this time their
target isn't the Ballman?
but his partner, Zoro!
This is about to get ugly!
HAMBURGER HEAVEN!
NO!
SORROW!
But the assault isn't over yet!
It pan-readies yet another brutal attack!
Hamburg is brandishing his mighty elbow
guards and preparing for
an ant-a-crown strike!
Oh, no! This is bad.
The Straw Hats are about to
learn the power of teamwork!
Like an arrow running from the sky! Huh?
Haunt attack!
No!
The rat cat?
He won't be walking that one off.
By the way, fatalities are a common
occurrence in the groggy ring,
in case you didn't know.
So dizzy.
And now the Foxy team turns their
attention to the straw-hack ballman!
You got...
Cannon!
Pickles and his spikes
are closing in fast!
Sanchi! Move!
Spring tackle!
What?
You thought that was it?
They're just getting started!
Attack?
Shepard sends them flying back.
They don't even care
about scoring anymore.
The Craggy Monster stopped the competition
flat with a spectacular
three-man team attack.
Such a cruel way to win.
Get up, Zoro.
Come on, Sanji.
Both balls are still in play,
but it looks like Team Straw
Hat is down for the count.
It's a kick.
In fact, you might say they're...
Now all that's left is to stuff
the ball man in his coffin.
I mean, goal.
And it'll be two wins in a
row for the Foxy Pirates.
It just goes to show you can't
keep a good monster down.
Looks like we win again.
Hey, let's work together for ten seconds.
Okay, fine.
But no longer.
Hey, wait, look.
They're out!
Against all odds The straw
hats are back on their feet.
Even after a demoralizing beatdown!
The swordsman without his
swords, and the seven-ship!
Stand tall in the face
of adversity once again!
Yeah!
You guys!
Why you gotta scare me like that?
The question is, even if they can stand,
do they have enough strength left to fight?
I have a little request.
One monster bagger, please!
uh huh now what could that
mean oh do you hear that
our boss has just ordered the
famous monster Starbarker!
I get that you guys are cheaters and
all, but can you at least try to hide it?
Does my pick go sour or sweet?
What are the toppings?
A head of green lettuce and
some fine yellow cheese.
Drafts between some big
pans, what do I say?
A monster burger for me
to eat. Here it comes!
The most terrifying triple attack!
The most horrifying hamburger!
It seems hopeless for the Straw Hats,
but I can't help but think
that the Corgi Monsters?
might get handed a red card for such
a flagrant violation of the rules.
But looking back, what a coincidence!
The referee just happens to be
doing some stretches right now.
Oh, well, he can't catch everything!
I'm gonna make you turn
around! Luffy, no! Why not?
They want you to get mad so you'll
butt in and do something stupid!
I just got a grin and fear it, Luffy.
The preparations are complete!
All that's left now is to sit
back and enjoy the carnage!
Whatever happens from here
on out, don't blame me.
Anyway, looks like they're going
straight for the ball, man.
If I bless the axe fast,
he'll be grounded, pounded,
spliced and diced, dragged and
smashed into a burger patty.
All right, then.
If you want a cooking battle, you got one.
Though I got to warn you, I've
never cooked scumbags before,
so I can't say how it'll turn out.
You are mincey. Bust you up.
Achy!
Petyo, shoot!
Stop crushing!
No! Hamburg!
You're gonna pay for that!
Hold up, fatty.
Forget about me.
Out of my way, small fry!
I'll cut you!
No sword style.
Tatsu?
Mock!
Oh, no!
Saiyan isn't so!
Big Pan has fallen victims of
pickle-spinning-play-to-man!
Somebody help me!
I can't stop spinning!
Bad Manor!
KICK COURSE!
Head?!
Not only did they knock Big Pan down,
they knocked him right back up too!
Although Big Pan is indeed on his feet,
I'm not sure if he has any
idea where he's at right now!
Uh-oh!
Now Zoro from the Straw
Hats is charging in!
Will he be able to overtake Big
Pan in his state of confusion?
You're not getting past me.
I've had enough of your crap!
And that goes for the ref too.
The crowd, or rather the ref?
Takes a direct hit from
the flying pickles!
You did that.
On purpose.
In your red car.
Wait a sec.
My whistle and my cards are gone.
You're such a naughty girl.
What can I say?
Old habits die hard.
Oh, this is bad.
Here they go again.
With victory in their grasp, the
Straw Hats turn on each other.
Oh, shame.
A medallion!
Power show!
Incredible!
Big Pan! What? No way!
The massive Wu-Tan warrior!
All right!
They headed for the gold ring!
It can't be!
Goal!